Okay, so lesson 10 then is resource
management part two.
And these are some of the learning
objectives.
So one of the things we
want to do is understand what
the difference is between a
leader and a manager, right?
Because we should always strive to be a
leader, right?
So we'll talk about some of the
differences between that, right?
So you need to understand the difference
in leaders and managers.
You will also learn the
different stages of team
development, something
called the Tuckman model.
So we'll talk about that in one of the
videos.
You also need to identify ways to track
team formers.
So we will discuss that over this section.
Also, conflicts.
Conflicts is a major part of a team.
Wherever you have people, you have
conflicts.
So you want to understand and appreciate
the purpose of conflict management.
Also, there's a difference in conflict
resolution and conflict management.
We'll talk about that.
So you want to understand
the difference in the two and
the purpose, really the
purpose of conflict management.
Also, something new that PMI have added to
the new exam is emotional intelligence.
We've got a few videos on emotional
intelligence, right?
So how does that impact your leadership
style?
So you need to understand
then the emotion, or rather you
need to understand the
importance of emotional intelligence.
And then finally, you also need some
motivational theories as well.
There's a few theories, HR
theories that you need to know for
the exam so just learn some
of these motivational theories